Guide to the R. A. (Revels Alcorn) Adams Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
R. A. (Revels Alcorn) Adams papers
1902-1945
JWJ MSS 48
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
6.35
(14 boxes)
The collection consists of writings, sheet music, scrapbooks, photographs, and other papers, stemming from R. A. Adams's activities as an evangelistic minister of the African Methodist Episcopal Church and as a writer, lecturer, and publisher of pamphlets on topics relating to race, religion, contraception, interpersonal relations, and socioeconomics. The collection documents aspects of African American religion and culture, especially in the South, in the early 20th century, and in particular the evangelistic, educational, and literary activities of one African American Methodist minister.
Adams, R. A. (Revels Alcorn), 1869-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from William Reese Co. on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund and Serendipity Books on the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts & Letters Fund, 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
R. A. (Revels Alcorn) Adams (b. 1869)
R. A. Adams was born on 28 February 1869 in Vicksburg, Mississippi. He attended Payne Theological Seminary in Wilberforce, Ohio, and served as a Methodist minister in Clarksdale, Brookhaven, Jackson, and Natchez, Mississippi. According to his own biographical statement, Adams entered the ministry, presumably of the African Methodist Episcopal Church, on 23 August 1891 and worked in the pastorate until 1910, after which time he traveled around the South and parts of the Midwest and Mid-Atlantic regions as an evangelist and lecturer. He wrote and lectured on the topics of religion, theology, philosophy, race, eugenics, prophylactics, and social behavior. As president and presumably founder of The Progress Publishing Co. in Wichita, Kansas, he collaborated on and published pamphlets on the same topics, including his own Highlights of Negro History, Psychoanalysis and Racial Affinity, and Syphilis, The Black Plague.
In addition to sermons and lectures, Adams also wrote novels, critical essays, poetry, and music, most, if not all, of which were never published. His novels include Babylon, described by Adams as "Religious - Sociological - Interracial - Stresses Gospel as Panacea for all Social Ills", Deacon Simpson, "Story of Negro Church Life - Contrasting Old, Unlettered Ministers with Modern Products - Evolution in Negro Church Life", and The Great Cathedral, "Exposure of Graft, Corruption, Autocracy, and Ecclesiastical Misfeasance - Predicting Revolution and Reformation of the Negro Church". His critical essays likewise explore the Negro Church in the late 19th and early 20th centuries, in addition to other topics, and include works such as "The Negro and His Church" and "The Negro Church - What Ails It?".
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of writings, sheet music, scrapbooks, photographs, and other papers, stemming from R. A. Adams's activities as an evangelistic minister of the African Methodist Episcopal Church and as a writer, lecturer, and publisher of pamphlets on topics relating to race, religion, contraception, interpersonal relations, and socioeconomics. The collection documents aspects of African American religion and culture, especially in the South, in the early 20th century, and in particular the evangelistic, educational, and literary activities of one African American Methodist minister.
Writings by Adams comprise the bulk of the collection and include typescripts, some of which are corrected, and manuscripts of addresses, sermons, and critical essays, as well as typescripts and manuscripts of creative works such as poetry, novels, and a play. Also included are typescripts of writings by others, on which Adams collaborated or which he seems to have published as president of The Progress Publishing Co.; as well as typescripts of musical programs and sheet music for songs by Adams; scrapbooks containing correspondence, letters of introduction, resolutions, testimonials, and clippings, documenting Adams's evangelistic activities from 1910 to 1921; photographs of Adams and his family; and printed material and other loose papers.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into four subseries: I. Writings, 1902-1944. II. Writings by Others, 1930s. III. Music, undated. IV. Other Papers, 1911-1945.
African American authors -- 20th Century; African American churches; African American clergy; African American Methodists; African American preaching; African Americans -- Religion -- 20th Century; American literature -- African American authors; Contraception; Economics -- Sociological aspects; Eugenics; Evangelistic work; Interpersonal relations; Race; Religion; Theology; Adams, R. A. (Revels Alcorn), 1869-; Bearer, A. G.; African Methodist Episcopal Church; Progress Publishing Co
- Writings, 1902-1944; Series I; 3.75; (9 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of typescripts, some of which are corrected, and manuscripts of creative, philosophical, religious, and educational works written by R. A. Adams.
  Arrangement
  Arranged into six subseries: Addresses, Novels, Plays, Poetry, Sermons, and Shorter Works.
  - Addresses
    - Letters and address, circa 1941, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous pages, typescript, corrected (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Untitled typescript, corrected (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - "The Battles of Peace", typescript, corrected (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - "Better trained and more consecrated ministry necessary to perpetuate the church among our people", typescript (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "From possibility to achievement", typescript, corrected (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - "Gospel minister and the community", typescript (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - "The Grammar of Duty", typescript, corrected (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - "Great Social Uplift Campaign", booklet, circa 1919 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - "Industrial Education", typescript, corrected (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - "Joy in Accomplishment", typescript (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - "Lecture I Chapters One - Four", typescripts (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - "Love the chief attribute in the character of God", typescript, corrected (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - "Milestones", typescript (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - "The Pastor a leader and guide in church worship", typescript (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - "The Pastor as leader in church worship", typescript (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - "Service", typescript, corrected (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - "The Story of Bethlehem", typescript (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - "Sunday school an asset to the church", typescript (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - "True mission of the gospel preacher", typescript (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - "Untrodden Paths", typescript (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - "Welcome address by the Rev. James Arthur", typescript (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - "What is required for a spiritual advance in the relation of the churches to the race problem", typescript, December 7, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Novels
    - "Babylon", typescript (Box 1, Folder 24-31)
    - "The Great Cathedral", typescript (Box 2, Folder 32-39)
    - "Deacon Simpson", typescript (Box 3, Folder 40-45)
    - Untitled novel (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Plays
    - "Daniel", typescript (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Poetry
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - "Anniversary Poems", typescript (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - "Complete Poetical Works of R.A. Adams, Volume Two, Book I: Characteristics of Love", typescript (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - "Complete Poetical Works of R.A. Adams, Volume Two, Book II: Diversities of Love", typescript (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - "Complete Poetical Works of R.A. Adams, Volume Two, Book III: Tragedies of Love", typescript (Box 3, Folder 51-52)
    - "Destiny of the sons of Noah", typescript (Box 3, Folder 53-55)
    - "Events of Passion Week", typescript
    - "Memorial Day Poetry, Memorial Day Prose, Independence Day Poetry", typescript (Box 3, Folder 56-57)
    - "The Messiah", Synopsis of Contents and Book I, typescript, corrected (Box 3, Folder 58-59)
    - Poetic Cullings, typscript (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - "Poetic Works, Volume One, Book I: Inspiration", typescript, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - "Poetic Works, Volume One, Book II: Heroism", typescript, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - "Poetic Works, Volume One, Book III: Service", typescript, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - "Poetic Works, Volume One, Book IV: Religious Life", typescript, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - "Poetic Works, Volume One, Books I-IV", duplicates (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - "Some Love poems", manuscript and typescript (Box 4, Folder 66-68)
    - Synopsis of poetical works of R.A. Adams with speciman pages from various volumes, typescript (Box 4, Folder 69-70)
    - Untitled collection of poetry by R.A. Adams, typescript (Box 4, Folder 71-72)
  - Sermons
    - "Annual Sermons", manuscript and typescript, corrected (Box 4, Folder 73-76)
    - "Bible Way of Salvation", typescript (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - "Church Extension - 2", typescript (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - "The Church of the Living God Is the Greatest Institution in the World", typescript (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Church service plan for special Sundays, typescript, corrected (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - "Consequence of rejecting reproof", typescript (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - "Defiant builders", typescript (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Doom of Death, an Easter Service, typescript (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - "Educational Sermon", typescript (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - "Ezekiel's vision and its lessons", typescript (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - "Good Tidings", manuscript (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - "The Gospel and Peace", typescript (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Gospel Minister and the Community, typescript (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - "The gospel minister as a witness", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - "Hell no. 3: the gulf between", typescript (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - "How about your conscience", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - "How I can be done", manuscript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - "Judgement by analogy", typescript (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - "The King of the Home", typescript (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - "Life means opportunity", typescript (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - "Marring our thanksgiving celebration", typescript (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - "Mary's lost child and yours compared", manuscript and typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - "Memorial day", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Memorial sermon, typescript (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - "Memories in hell", typescript (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - "The mission of free masonry", typescript (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - "The need of consecrated workers", typescript (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - "Our building and its master-builder", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - "Parable of the eagle's nest", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - "Parson's personal problems", manuscript (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - "Passing of Helen Brook", manuscript (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - "Power of the Gospel", manuscript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - "Question of hell", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - "Rainy day", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - "Role of church in the changing world", typescript (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - "Salvation to the uttermost", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Sermons, typescript and manuscript, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Sermon notes, notebooks (Box 5, Folder 113-115)
    - Sermons and Addresses, typescript (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Sermons for young men, typescript (Box 5, Folder 117-118)
    - "Shall we keep faith with the dead", typescript (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - "Sins of Youth" and other sermons, typescript (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - "So eleven indictments are brought against these roaming heretics", typescript (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - "Sowing and Reaping #4", typescript (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Special addresses and sermons, typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 123-125)
    - "Stanza One", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - "Story of Calvary", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - "The street called straight", typescript, corrected (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - "Subject: Exposure of excuses", typescript (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - "Subject: The Great Commission", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - "Subject: Jesus Christ the source from which all of our needs may be supplied", typescript (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - "Subject: The lights that failed", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - "Subject: The man without a wedding garment", typescript (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - "Subject: Parental righteousness", typescript (Box 6, Folder 134-135)
    - "Subject: Refusing God's call", typescript (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - "Subject: The wretched sinner", typescript (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - "Suffer them to come unto me", typescript (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - "Text, Matt. 2:16. Out of Egypt I have called me son", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - "Text-Matt. 11:7 ... 'St. John the Baptist'", typescript, correct (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - "Text- Num. 32:23 / Subject- Exposure of sin inevitable", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - "Theme: Fixing Responsibility", typescript (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - "Theme: The foolish virgin", typescript (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - "Theme: The refuge of lies", typescript (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - "Theme: Sold for naught", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - "Utterly Abandoned",typescript (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - "War and Peace",typescript (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Weekly Short Sermons, typescript, 1931, undated (Box 6, Folder 148-150)
    - "What is sin?", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - "Who is on the Lord's Side?", typescript (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - "Worship God", typescript (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - "Your father and mine", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Shorter Works
    - "Apostrophe to death", typescript (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - "Architecture", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - "Astronomy", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - Autobiographical statement, typescript (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - "The awful curse of illegitimacy", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 159)
    - "Ben Oni", typescript (Box 6, Folder 160-161)
    - "Bible Mothers", typescript (Box 6, Folder 162-163)
    - "Bible Wives and Bible Mothers", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 164-165)
    - "Book Agriculture", typescript (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - "Can the Church Survive?", typescript (Box 6, Folder 167-169)
    - "Can You Define It?" printed version (Box 6, Folder 170)
    - "Chapter I: Mathematics", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 171)
    - "Confessions of a Philanderer", typescript (Box 6, Folder 172-173)
    - "Crowning Sin of Womanhood", typescript, corrected (Box 6, Folder 174)
    - "The Crux of the Criminal Situation", typescript (Box 6, Folder 175-176)
    - "Cullings and Comments, Volume III", typescript (Box 6, Folder 177)
    - "Defence of Beautiful Isle", typescript (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - "Double Moral Standard", typescript, corrected (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - "Eugenics", manuscript and typescript, corrected (Box 7, Folder 180-184)
    - "I: The Exodus: Cause and Effect", typescript, corrected (Box 7, Folder 185)
    - "Fallacies Exposed", typescript (Box 7, Folder 186-187)
    - "Funeral", typescript (Box 7, Folder 188)
    - "Further analysis of sin", typescript, corrected (Box 7, Folder 189)
    - "Glorious Death", typescript (Box 7, Folder 190-191)
    - "Hallucinitis", typescript (Box 7, Folder 192-193)
    - "Heroes Unsung", typescript (Box 7, Folder 194-195)
    - "Highlights of Negro History", printed version (Box 7, Folder 196)
    - "Home Life", typescript (Box 7, Folder 197)
    - "Ideal Womanhood", typescript, corrected (Box 7, Folder 198)
    - "Immortality and Crime", typescript, corrected (Box 7, Folder 199)
    - "Indulgent Mothers", typescript (Box 7, Folder 200)
    - "Inequity of the Double Moral Standard", typescript, corrected (Box 7, Folder 201)
    - "Light on race adjustment", typescript, corrected (Box 7, Folder 202)
    - "Longfellow's philosophy of life", typescript (Box 7, Folder 203)
    - "Menace of lust", typescript, corrected (Box 7, Folder 204)
    - "Mothers of men", typescript corrected (Box 7, Folder 205)
    - "The Negro and His Church", manuscript and typescript (Box 7, Folder 206-209)
    - "Negro and the nation", typescript (Box 8, Folder 210-211)
    - "The Negro Church- What Ails It?", typescript (Box 8, Folder 212)
    - "One Church", typescript (Box 8, Folder 213-214)
    - "Our Young People", typescript (Box 8, Folder 215)
    - "Philosophical Trends", typescript (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - "Physics of Natural History", typescript, corrected (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - "Pioneers", typescript, corrected (Box 8, Folder 218)
    - "Practical Hymnology", printed version, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 219)
    - "Pronunciation Plus Division One Biblical Proper Nouns", typescript (Box 8, Folder 220)
    - "Psychoanalysis and Racial Affinity", printed version (Box 8, Folder 221)
    - "Question of Engagement", typescript, corrected (Box 8, Folder 222)
    - "Quotations from Negro Authors", typescript (Box 8, Folder 223)
    - "Remade Men", typescript, corrected (Box 8, Folder 224)
    - "Revival Hymns", printed version (Box 8, Folder 225)
    - "Ritualisitic Revision", typescript (Box 8, Folder 226)
    - "Select Hymns", printed version, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 227)
    - "Sense vs. Sound in Singing", typescript (Box 8, Folder 228-229)
    - "Serious Anthology", typescript (Box 8, Folder 230)
    - "Shall we stabilize our moral system?", typescript, corrected (Box 8, Folder 231)
    - "Society and its criminals", typescript, corrected (Box 8, Folder 232)
    - "The Songs We Sing", typescript (Box 8, Folder 233-235)
    - "Sowing and Reaping", typescript (Box 8, Folder 236)
    - "Stories of Mothers", manuscript (Box 8, Folder 237)
    - "Story of Bethlehem", typescript (Box 8, Folder 238)
    - "Study of Verbs and Auxiliary Verbs", typescript (Box 8, Folder 239)
    - "Syphilis / the Black Plague", printed version, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 240)
    - "Tennyson's Christmas Sermon (the writer's interpretation of 'Ring Out Wild Bells')", typescript (Box 8, Folder 241)
    - "Texts and Topics", typescript (Box 8, Folder 242)
    - "Things Worthwhile", typescript (Box 8, Folder 243)
    - "Topics and Texts", typescript (Box 8, Folder 244-245)
    - "Tragedies of Love", typescript (Box 8, Folder 246-248)
    - "What I Believe", typescript, corrected (Box 8, Folder 249)
    - "What Others Say About Us", typescript (Box 8, Folder 250)
    - "When Negros Pray", typescript (Box 9, Folder 251)
    - [Women] "The Young Woman and Her Problems", typescript, corrected (Box 9, Folder 252)
    - [Women] "The Young Woman and the Social Evils", typescript, corrected (Box 9, Folder 253)
    - [Women] "Oblation", typescript, corrected (Box 9, Folder 254)
    - [Women] "Her Personal Problems", manuscript (Box 9, Folder 255)
    - [Women] "The Problems of Mothers", typescript, corrected (Box 9, Folder 256)
    - [Women] "Physical Degeneracy", typescript (Box 9, Folder 257)
    - [Women] "Transcendent Motherhood", typescript (Box 9, Folder 258)
    - [Women] Miscellaneous pages about women, typescript (Box 9, Folder 259)
    - "Your Family and Mine", typescript (Box 9, Folder 260)
    - "Your Father and Mine", typescript (Box 9, Folder 261-263)
    - Fragments, manuscript and typescript (Box 9, Folder 264-267)
    - Untitled works, typescripts (Box 9, Folder 268-275)
- Writings By Others, 1930s; Series II; 0.42; (1 box)
  This series consists of typescripts of works, mainly on religious topics, written by others. Many were written in collaboration with R. A. Adams and were published by him under The Progress Publishing Co.
  Arranged alphabetically by author and then by title.
  - Bearer, A. G., in collaboration with R. A. Adams
    - "Bible Fathers and Bible Mothers", typescript (Box 10, Folder 276-277)
    - "Bible Perverts", typescript (Box 10, Folder 278-279)
    - "Bible Wives and Bible Mothers", typescript (Box 10, Folder 280)
    - "Parables of our Lord", typescript (Box 10, Folder 281-282)
    - "Social Sins", typescript, corrected (Box 10, Folder 283-284)
    - "Weekly Short Sermons", typescript (Box 10, Folder 285-288)
    - "Weekly Short Sermons for boys", typescript (Box 10, Folder 289-290)
  - Gregg, John A., "Of Men and Of Arms", typescript (Box 10, Folder 291)
  - Horsey, G. E., "The Challenge of Efficiency in the Work and Leadership of the Christian Ministry!", typescript (Box 10, Folder 292)
  - Horsey, G. E., "The Pastor's Role in Man's Salvation", typescript (Box 10, Folder 293)
  - Ish, Videtta, in collaboration with R. A. Adams, "Looking Back", typescript (Box 10, Folder 294-296)
  - McAllister, Rev. C. Lopez, "Working with God", typescript (Box 10, Folder 297-298)
  - Mann, A. B., in collaboration with R. A. Adams
    - "Habits", typescript, corrected (Box 10, Folder 299-300)
    - "Myths and Morals", typescript (Box 10, Folder 301)
  - "Madam X", in collaboration with R. A. Adams, "My Wife and Others", typescript (Box 10, Folder 302)
  - Mr. "X" in collaboration with R. A. Adams, "These Husbands of Ours", typescript (Box 10, Folder 303)
- Music, undated; Series III; 0.42; (2 boxes)
  This series consists of typescripts of musical programs dramatizing Bible stories and other religious topics, and sheet music for what appear to be songs by R. A. Adams.
  Arranged by format.
  - "Music, Programs and Dramas: Bible Stories Dramatized", typescript, corrected (Box 11, Folder 304)
  - "Music, Programs and Dramas: Story of Bethlehem", typescript, corrected (Box 11, Folder 305)
  - "Music, Programs and Dramas: The doom of death, an Easter service", typescript, corrected (Box 11, Folder 306)
  - "Music, Programs and Dramas: The House of Many Mansions", typescript, corrected (Box 11, Folder 307)
  - "Music, Programs and Dramas", manuscript and typescript, corrected (Box 11, Folder 308)
  - Sheet Music, manuscript and typescript (Box 11, Folder 309)
  - Sheet Music, manuscript and typescript (Box 12, Folder 310-315)
- Other Papers, 1911-1945; Series IV; 0.42; (1 box)
  This series consists of scrapbooks, photographs, letters, and printed material, variously documenting the evangelistic and literary activities of R. A. Adams.
  Arranged in rough chronological order.
  - Scrapbook of correspondence, letters of introduction, resolutions and testimonials relating to R. A. Adams and his evangelistic activities, 1910-1919 (Box 13, Folder 316)
  - Scrapbook of clippings documenting R. A. Adams and his evangelistic activities, 1916-1921 (Box 13, Folder 317)
  - Photographs, R. A. Adams (Box 13, Folder 318)
  - Photograph, Adams Family (Box 13, Folder 319)
  - Letter to R. A. Adams from Jennie Seamon, Eva Stewart and Margaret Wood (Box 13, Folder 320)
  - An open letter to Christian Herald, typescript, corrected, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 321)
  - Form letter regarding the education of African-Americans, undated (Box 13, Folder 322-323)
  - Literary Productions of R.A. Adams, list, typescript (Box 13, Folder 324)
  - Calling Card (Box 13, Folder 325)
  - Celebration Golden Anniversary Offering Envelopes, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 326)
  - Envelopes (Box 13, Folder 327)
  - Printed material (Box 13, Folder 328-329)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also Oversize, Box 14
  - "Schedule of Kansas City District", 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 330)
  - Statement, Adams Printing Company, circa 1935 (Box 13, Folder 331)
  - Original Folders with notes on them (Box 13, Folder 332-335)
- Oversize, 1.34; (1 box)
  - Poetry, "Events of Passion Week", typescript (from Series I) (Box 14 (Oversize), Folder 336)